// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q004: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Guests at Hayworth Hotel can ------ access most of the city’s tourist attractions.',
      choices: ['easy', 'ease', 'easier', 'easily'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['easily'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q031',
    },
    {
      question: 'TAT Studio required that new employees ------ a training report within a week.',
      choices: ['submit', 'submitted', 'had submitted', 'were submitted'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['submit'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q032',
    },
    {
      question: 'Please note that parking outside of designated areas in national parks is subject to a ------.',
      choices: ['prediction', 'fine', 'warranty', 'committee'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['fine'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q033',
    },
    {
      question: 'The ------ for the public library submitted by Astra Design Corporation exceeded the budget of the City of Riverdale.',
      choices: ['estimating', 'estimator', 'estimated', 'estimate'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['estimate'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q034',
    },
    {
      question: '------ the building application has been approved, construction can begin on the KEP Building.',
      choices: ['Upon', 'Now that', 'Afterward', 'Although'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Now that'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q035',
    },
    {
      question: 'Star Light Airlines has been looking for a senior accountant for the past six months, but the position ------ open.',
      choices: ['contains', 'hires', 'holds', 'remains'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['remains'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q036',
    },
    {
      question: 'Beginners in programming can learn the basics in the ------ course offered by TEC School.',
      choices: ['introductory', 'introduced', 'introducing', 'introduce'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['introductory'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q037',
    },
    {
      question: '------ attending the craft workshop next weekend will receive free materials.',
      choices: ['Whoever', 'Anything', 'Who', 'Anyone'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Anyone'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q038',
    },
    {
      question: 'As a result of long-term requests from local residents, construction of the sports center will ------ in June.',
      choices: ['commence', 'modify', 'predict', 'establish'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['commence'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q039',
    },
    {
      question: 'Extensive ------ is needed to find the causes related to recent climate change.',
      choices: ['analyst', 'analyze', 'analysis', 'analytic'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['analysis'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題031-040/#q040',
    },
  ],
}